dealsbell.com 2013-12-19

# Privacy policy «

Dealsbell.com believes in providing quality customer service and makes realistic efforts to protect the privacy of its customers. We value our customers and respect their privacy and expect authentic details from our customers.Please read this policy very carefully before sharing any personal information.

**INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT:**

You may be asked to provide certain information such as name, email address and postal address.

The data which we collect from our customers is very confidential. We are not disclosing any information to any third party. We may use this data to provide information regarding the latest deals and offers to you.

Please note that we are not responsible for any claim made by the visitors to our site regarding not getting the discount amount, as we are just affiliated with the company and promoting their products and deals through links. So, if any visitor facing problem in discount amount than you will be responsible to handle his/her problem.

**ACCESS TO AND MODIFYING PERSONAL INFORMATION:**

If you would like to make any changes in your personal information, than you can do it through mail to us at affiliate@dealsbell.com. And we will edit your personal information as per your choice.

**CONSENT TO PRIVACY POLICY:**

After accepting our terms and conditions and providing with the necessary information to us, you are liable to use our service. You can visit our site frequently for changes or updates any.

**CHANGES IN PRIVACY POLICY:**

There may be some slight changes from time to time in our Privacy policy. We will surely obtain your consent if there are some major changes or updates to our Privacy Policy.

If you have any concerns regarding our comfort, you can get in touch with the Organization via e-mail at [affiliate@dealsbell.com](mailto:affiliate@dealsbell.com)
